{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "x^9 / 2 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n1 / 2x^-9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-16x^2", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-(4x)^2 / 1\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n-1 * 16x^2 / 1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-1 / (4x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7 / 4x^8", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n7x^-8 / 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8x^2", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-(4x)^2 / 2\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n-1 * 16x^2 / 2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-1 / 2(4x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 / 3 ", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n(2x)^2 / 3\n(2x)^2 simplifies into 4x^2\n1 * 4x^2 / 3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n1 / 3(2x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "54x^3", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n2(3x)^3 / 1\n(3x)^3 simplifies into 27x^3\n2 * 27x^3 / 1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2 / (3x)^-3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5 / 16x", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n5 / 4(4x)\n(4x) simplifies into 4x\n5 / 4 * 4x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5(4x)^-1 / 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x / 2 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5 / 2x^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5 / 14x", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n5 / 7(2x)\n(2x) simplifies into 2x\n5 / 7 * 2x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5(2x)^-1 / 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5 / 4x", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5x^-1 / 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9x / 4 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-9 / 4x^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 36x^2", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n1 / 4(3x)^2\n(3x)^2 simplifies into 9x^2\n1 / 4 * 9x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x)^-2 / 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x / 8 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n1 / 8x^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9x / 2 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-9 / 2x^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^8 / 9 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5 / 9x^-8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-(4x) / 2\n(4x) simplifies into 4x\n-1 * 4x / 2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-1 / 2(4x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "81x^3 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n3(3x)^3 / 5\n(3x)^3 simplifies into 27x^3\n3 * 27x^3 / 5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3 / 5(3x)^-3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2 / 9x", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n2 / 3(3x)\n(3x) simplifies into 3x\n2 / 3 * 3x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2(3x)^-1 / 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5 / 12x^2", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n5 / 3(2x)^2\n(2x)^2 simplifies into 4x^2\n5 / 3 * 4x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5(2x)^-2 / 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^2", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-1 / x^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^2", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-(3x)^2 / 3\n(3x)^2 simplifies into 9x^2\n-1 * 9x^2 / 3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-1 / 3(3x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "96x^3", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n3(4x)^3 / 2\n(4x)^3 simplifies into 64x^3\n3 * 64x^3 / 2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3 / 2(4x)^-3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2 / x", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n4 / (2x)\n(2x) simplifies into 2x\n4 / 1 * 2x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4(2x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 16x^3", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n4 / (4x)^3\n(4x)^3 simplifies into 64x^3\n4 / 1 * 64x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4(4x)^-3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x / 5 ", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-(3x) / 5\n(3x) simplifies into 3x\n-1 * 3x / 5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-1 / 5(3x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3 / 8x^2", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n3 / 2(2x)^2\n(2x)^2 simplifies into 4x^2\n3 / 2 * 4x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3(2x)^-2 / 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-15x", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-5(3x) / 1\n(3x) simplifies into 3x\n-5 * 3x / 1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-5 / (3x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 16x", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n1 / 4(4x)\n(4x) simplifies into 4x\n1 / 4 * 4x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^-1 / 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4 / 3x", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n4 / (3x)\n(3x) simplifies into 3x\n4 / 1 * 3x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4(3x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "16x^2 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n(4x)^2 / 5\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n1 * 16x^2 / 5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n1 / 5(4x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "20x^2", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n5(4x)^2 / 4\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n5 * 16x^2 / 4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5 / 4(4x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-4(3x) / 3\n(3x) simplifies into 3x\n-4 * 3x / 3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-4 / 3(3x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "36x^2 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n4(3x)^2 / 5\n(3x)^2 simplifies into 9x^2\n4 * 9x^2 / 5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4 / 5(3x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^7 / 3 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n8 / 3x^-7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12x^2 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n3(2x)^2 / 5\n(2x)^2 simplifies into 4x^2\n3 * 4x^2 / 5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3 / 5(2x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-9x^2 / 2 ", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-(3x)^2 / 2\n(3x)^2 simplifies into 9x^2\n-1 * 9x^2 / 2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-1 / 2(3x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x / 5 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n9 / 5x^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "16x^2 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n(4x)^2 / 5\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n1 * 16x^2 / 5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n1 / 5(4x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 12x^2", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n4 / 3(4x)^2\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n4 / 3 * 16x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4(4x)^-2 / 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "24x^3 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n3(2x)^3 / 5\n(2x)^3 simplifies into 8x^3\n3 * 8x^3 / 5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3 / 5(2x)^-3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-7 / 4x^9", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-7x^-9 / 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x^8 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n9 / 5x^-8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x^7 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n9 / 5x^-7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^3", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-(2x)^3 / 2\n(2x)^3 simplifies into 8x^3\n-1 * 8x^3 / 2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-1 / 2(2x)^-3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^6", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2 / x^-6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^2", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n3(2x)^2 / 2\n(2x)^2 simplifies into 4x^2\n3 * 4x^2 / 2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3 / 2(2x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "16x^2", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n4(2x)^2 / 1\n(2x)^2 simplifies into 4x^2\n4 * 4x^2 / 1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4 / (2x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8x", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-2(4x) / 1\n(4x) simplifies into 4x\n-2 * 4x / 1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-2 / (4x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^2 / 8 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5 / 8x^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4 / 9x", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n4 / 3(3x)\n(3x) simplifies into 3x\n4 / 3 * 3x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4(3x)^-1 / 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5 / 16x^3", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n5 / 2(2x)^3\n(2x)^3 simplifies into 8x^3\n5 / 2 * 8x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5(2x)^-3 / 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5 / 6x^2", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5x^-2 / 6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "x", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n(2x) / 2\n(2x) simplifies into 2x\n1 * 2x / 2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n1 / 2(2x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x / 5 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2 / 5x^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3 / 16x", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n3 / 4(4x)\n(4x) simplifies into 4x\n3 / 4 * 4x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3(4x)^-1 / 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-32x^2 / 3 ", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-2(4x)^2 / 3\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n-2 * 16x^2 / 3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-2 / 3(4x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7 / 9x", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n7x^-1 / 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 48x^3", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n4 / 3(4x)^3\n(4x)^3 simplifies into 64x^3\n4 / 3 * 64x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4(4x)^-3 / 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 18x^3", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n3 / 2(3x)^3\n(3x)^3 simplifies into 27x^3\n3 / 2 * 27x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3(3x)^-3 / 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 36x^2", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n4 / 9(4x)^2\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n4 / 9 * 16x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4(4x)^-2 / 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2 / 3x^4", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2x^-4 / 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 6x^2", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n2 / 3(2x)^2\n(2x)^2 simplifies into 4x^2\n2 / 3 * 4x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2(2x)^-2 / 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12x^2", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n3(2x)^2 / 1\n(2x)^2 simplifies into 4x^2\n3 * 4x^2 / 1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3 / (2x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-16x", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-4(4x) / 1\n(4x) simplifies into 4x\n-4 * 4x / 1\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-4 / (4x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1 / 7x^5", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-x^-5 / 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x / 2 ", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n7(2x) / 4\n(2x) simplifies into 2x\n7 * 2x / 4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n7 / 4(2x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3 / 56x^3", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n3 / 7(2x)^3\n(2x)^3 simplifies into 8x^3\n3 / 7 * 8x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3(2x)^-3 / 7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2 / x^9", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2x^-9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 16x^3", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n4 / (4x)^3\n(4x)^3 simplifies into 64x^3\n4 / 1 * 64x^3\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4(4x)^-3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-x^3", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-1 / x^-3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3 / 4x^9", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3x^-9 / 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7 / 9x^5", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n7x^-5 / 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^9", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2 / x^-9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5 / 8x^2", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n5 / 2(2x)^2\n(2x)^2 simplifies into 4x^2\n5 / 2 * 4x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5(2x)^-2 / 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2 / 5x^9", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2x^-9 / 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x / 5 ", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n(4x) / 5\n(4x) simplifies into 4x\n1 * 4x / 5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n1 / 5(4x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4 / 45x^2", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n4 / 5(3x)^2\n(3x)^2 simplifies into 9x^2\n4 / 5 * 9x^2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4(3x)^-2 / 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^6 / 9 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4 / 9x^-6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^4 / 3 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4 / 3x^-4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "48x^2 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n3(4x)^2 / 5\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n3 * 16x^2 / 5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3 / 5(4x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^6", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n4 / x^-6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "27x^3 / 2 ", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n(3x)^3 / 2\n(3x)^3 simplifies into 27x^3\n1 * 27x^3 / 2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n1 / 2(3x)^-3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2 / 9x", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n2 / 3(3x)\n(3x) simplifies into 3x\n2 / 3 * 3x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2(3x)^-1 / 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^6 / 9 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5 / 9x^-6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^4 / 4 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3 / 4x^-4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-24x^2", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-3(4x)^2 / 2\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n-3 * 16x^2 / 2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-3 / 2(4x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-112x^3", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n-7(4x)^3 / 4\n(4x)^3 simplifies into 64x^3\n-7 * 64x^3 / 4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-7 / 4(4x)^-3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x / 5 ", "explanation": "Because 2x is raised to a negative power, we move 2x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n2(2x) / 5\n(2x) simplifies into 2x\n2 * 2x / 5\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2 / 5(2x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^5 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-4 / 5x^-5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "24x^2", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n3(4x)^2 / 2\n(4x)^2 simplifies into 16x^2\n3 * 16x^2 / 2\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3 / 2(4x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 2x", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n2 / (4x)\n(4x) simplifies into 4x\n2 / 1 * 4x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2(4x)^-1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3 / 8x^5", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3x^-5 / 8", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1 / 12x", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n1 / 3(4x)\n(4x) simplifies into 4x\n1 / 3 * 4x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n(4x)^-1 / 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2 / 9x^2", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n2x^-2 / 9", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^6 / 7 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n5 / 7x^-6", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7x^2 / 5 ", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n7 / 5x^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8 / x^7", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-8x^-7", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-1 / 3x^2", "explanation": "Because x is raised to a negative power, we move x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n", "question": "Simplify:\n-x^-2 / 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x^2 / 4 ", "explanation": "Because 3x is raised to a negative power, we move 3x into the numerator and make the power positive.\n(3x)^2 / 4\n(3x)^2 simplifies into 9x^2\n1 * 9x^2 / 4\n", "question": "Simplify:\n1 / 4(3x)^-2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3 / 16x", "explanation": "Because 4x is raised to a negative power, we move 4x into the denominator and make the power positive.\n3 / 4(4x)\n(4x) simplifies into 4x\n3 / 4 * 4x\n", "question": "Simplify:\n3(4x)^-1 / 4", "type": "text"}
]}